声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
一本特别的书
Hell of a book.
写的是 我的性感女郎
It's about bunnies.
泳衣也不穿一定很冷吧
It must be cold without your trunks.
那当然
You bet.
靠近一点给我暖暖身子怎样?
How about you come a little closer and warm me up?
你很擅长于给女孩子带来新奇感  Sawyer
You sure know how to make a girl feel special, Sawyer.
你真让人不可思议  Sawyer
You're incredible, Sawyer.
我爱你
I love you.
看看你
Look at you.
现在你想要什么?
What do you want right now?
我怎么可能还会奢望其它东西?
How could I want anything else?
-宝贝儿  -什么?
-baby.  -what?
-你不是有个会议吗!  -有 但3:30再开呢
-I thought you had a meeting.  -Yeah, but it's not till 3:30.
宝贝儿已经3:28了
Baby, it's 3:28.
该死!
Damn it!
该死! 宝贝儿  为什么你不...
Damn it! Baby, why don't you just...
你去吧  你就走吧? 我呆在这儿
No, just go. You go, okay? I'll stay here.
我可以叫客房服务好好把自己吃胖
Order room service, get fat.
为什么不点个巧克力圣代?
Why don't you order a chocolate sundae.
我回来的时候
When I get back
我会把你当点心吃
I'll use you as a dish
这真不应该被你看到
You weren't exactly supposed to see that.
你翻我东西干什么  小子?
What're you doing in my stuff, son?
你有的好受了
This is gonna hurt.
告诉我发生什么事了?
Ready to tell me what happened?
我们正试图找出求救信号的来源
We were trying to find the sourceof the distress call.
我先看到了来自海边的信号灯
I saw the flare from the beach
然后看到了Sawyer在丛林中发出的信号
and then the flare from Sawyer's position in the jungle.
我启动天线装置
I switched on my antenna
激活接收机
activated the transceiver...
然后
...and then
眼前一片黑
darkness
有人从后面袭击了我
Whoever hit me came from behind
-还毁坏了设备?  -是的
-They destroyed the equipment?  -Yes.
听着  我们会把事情搞清楚的但不要做任何...
Listen, we're gonna figure this out, but don't do any...
为了找出肇事者  该怎么做我就怎么做
I will do what I need to do to find the man responsible.
我们这儿需要帮助!
We need some help over here!
发生什么事了?
What happened?
Sawyer
-晨间递送  -你真好  谢谢
-Morning delivery.  -Oh, you're sweet. Thanks.
我想依你现在的状况
Well, I figured in your condition
外加这个大肚子
with the extra baggage, you know
我还可以走 -勉强可以
Well, I can still walk.-Barely.
不管怎样我很担心你 你知道这儿太阳很厉害
Anyway, I worry about you out here. You know, it's very...sunny.
我有帽子遮挡
Thus my hat.
但你知道山洞那儿的帽子更多
You know, there's plenty of hats in the caves.
而且还有个医生随叫随到
And we got a doctor there as well. That will come in handy.
我喜欢海边 Charlie  -哦
I like the beach, Charlie.  -Yeah.
谁会愿意成天和沙蚤呆在一起?
Who wouldn't want to spend the day with sand fleas?
我愿意呆这儿  直到我们获救
I want to be here. For when we get rescued.
直到我们获救
When we get rescued.
对
Right
Jack  我没事
Jack, it's fine.
擦伤而已
It's just a scrape.
是擦伤  不过是大面积擦伤
Yeah. Lots of scrapes today.
双氧水快没了
I'm running out of peroxide.
-他扑到我身上  -为什么?
-He just jumped me, man. -Why?
Shannon有哮喘病
Shannon has asthma.
-哮喘?  -是的
-Asthma?  -Yeah.
我还没看到她发作过
Never seen her have an attack before.
那是因为她有个呼吸器
Because she had an inhaler.
没人注意的时候就偷偷的用
She sneaks hits when no one's looking.
当她还是个孩子的时候就以这为耻
She's just been embarrassed about it since she was a little kid.
我猜用呼吸器呼吸并不舒服
I guess breathing's not cool.
有个呼吸器? -几天前用完了
Had an inhaler?-It ran out a couple days ago.
不过还有四个替换药瓶可以够用几个月
But it had four refills, which should have been enough for a couple months.
但她老忘记换药所以我就把它们放在我的箱子内
But she always forgets her medication, so I put it in my suitcase.
今天我看到那个混帐在看"海底沉舟"(小说名)
Today I see that jackass reading "Watership Down"...
你把我弄糊涂了
You're losing me.
那是我包里的东西 我登机前注册过的
It was in my bags...the stuff that I checked.
如果他有我的那本书那他就会有我的行李
If he has my book, he has my luggage.
如果他有我的行李那就一定有呼吸器
If he has the luggage, he has the inhalers.
今天她的呼吸变得真的很困难
Her breathing got really rough today, man.
如果哮喘发作事情会很不妙的
If she has an attack, it's not gonna be good.
-它在哪?  -医生  好久不见
-Where is it?  -Hey, doc. Long time, no see.
-它在哪?  -什么在哪?
-Where is it?  -Where's what?
那女孩的哮喘药
The girl's asthma medicine.
Shannon她的呼吸器
Shannon. Her inhalers.
那个啊
that.
你打了一个试图帮助妹妹的孩子
You attacked a kid for trying to help his sick sister.
我大喊小偷是因为他在翻我的东西
I whooped a thief 'cause he was going through my stuff.
你的? 怎么会是你的?  -我不得不采取行动
Yours? What makes it yours?  -Which I had to move...
你从人家的提箱内拿走的东西怎么会是你的?
You can just take something out of a suitcase, and that makes it yours?
我不知道你们这些山顶洞人有多么奉行共产主义
Look,I don't know want kind of commie share-fest you're running over in cave town
但这儿所有东西是一九分
but down here possession's 9/10s
人有权保护他的财产
A man's got a right to protect his property.
起来!
Get up!
干吗?  想比谁高?
Why, you wanna see who's taller?
起来!
Get up!
你确定要摊这趟浑水?
You sure you want to make this your problem, doc?
是的  我确定
yeah. I'm sure.
这儿怎么回事?
What's going on here?
你说过你要去巴顿党(黑社会组织名)作交易
You told me you were going to Baton Rouge to close a deal.
相信我就是了  我没时间解释我已经迟到了
Just trust me. There isn't any time to explain. I'm already late.
如果我错过了这个会议整个交易就泡汤了  明白?
If I miss this meeting, the whole deal's a bust, all right?
那是我的全部  140000美元
That's everything I have. $140,000.
墨西哥湾有个油矿开采钻井平台
There's an oil mining operation in the gulf of Mexico. Drilling platforms.
花300000美金就可以参股
$300,000 buys you one share.
但只要你投资了
But as soon as you invest
由政府发起的基金会就会集资在两周内将你的投资增值三倍
a government-sponsored fund kicks in and triples your money in two weeks.
-300000美金?  -是的
-$300,000?  -Yeah.
你只有140000美金?
You got $140,000?
我在多伦多找了个投资者他要五五分成
I found an investor in Toronto. He wants in 50/50.
两周内我们差不多可以平分100万美金
Two weeks, we'll be splitting almost a million bucks.
Jess这是个机会
Jess, this is my chance.
还有个选择
There's another option.
是么?  说说看?
Yeah? What's that?
我给你160000美金然后利润我们平分
That I give you the $160,000 and we split the profit.
你到哪儿去弄160,000美金?
Yeah, and how in the hell are you gonna scare up 160,000 bucks?
我丈夫
My husband.
我要杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
就算那样  我们也拿不到药
That's not gonna help us get the medicine.
或许拿不到但至少感觉很爽
Maybe not, but it'll feel good.
那是什么阻止你这样做?
So what's stopping you?
我们还不是野人  Kate
We're not savages, Kate.
是还不是
Not yet.
让我去和Sawyer谈谈
Let me talk to sawyer.
你凭什么认为他会听你的?
What makes you think he's gonna listen to you?
他说我们有点关系
He says we have a connection.
-有吗?  -求你了
-Do you?  -Please.
你要什么?
What do you want?
再说一遍?
Excuse me?
你想要什么Sawyer?
What do you want, Sawyer?
雀斑女  对于这个问题我可以给你很多个答案
Freckles, I got so many answers to that question,
我都不知道从哪说起
I wouldn't even know where to start.
用什么可以换呼吸器?
What do you want for the inhalers?
问的好  让我想想
Good question. Hang on a tick.
我想要什么?
What do I want?
一个亲吻应该可以
A kiss ought to do it.
-什么?  -一个吻
-What?  -A kiss.
你的吻  就现在
From you, right now.
我不会买的
I don't buy it.
-买什么?  -这个交易
-Buy what?  -The act.
你太过分了Sawyer
You try too hard, Sawyer.
我请你去帮个不能呼吸的姑娘而你却要我亲你?
I ask you to help a woman who can't breathe, and you want me to kiss you?
没人比你更恶心了
Nobody's that disgusting.
-你要知道我看到过你  -看到我什么?
-I've seen you, you know.  -Seen me what?
那张纸你藏口袋里的那张纸
With that piece of paper. The one you keep in your pocket.
你念那张纸的时候我看到你的表情了
I've seen the expression on your face when you read it
你多么小心翼翼地把它折好那一定对你意味着什么
and how carefully you fold it up. It means something to you.
你可以随心所欲的玩游戏
So you can play games all you want
但我知道你内心的某个地方惦记着一个人
but I know there's a human being in there somewhere.
把药给我
Give me the medication.
你自以为你了解我
You think you understand me.
是的  我认为我...   -闭嘴!
Yeah. I think I...  -Shut up!
你想知道我是怎样一个人是吧?
You want to know what kind of human being I am?
念
Read it.
念!
大声一点
Out loud.
"亲爱的Sawyer先生"
Dear Mr. Sawyer,
"你不认识我"
you don't know who I am
"但我认识你"
but I know who you are
"而且我知道你做过什么"
and I know what you've done
"你和我妈妈上过床"
You had sex with my mother
"然后你又偷走了我爸爸的钱"
and then you stole my dad's money all away.
"所以他变的很愤怒"
So he got angry
"他杀了我妈妈"
and he killed my mother
然后也杀了他自己"
And then he killed himself, too."
不要停下来
Don't stop now.
后面更精彩
You're getting to the good part.
"我只知道你的名字"
All I know is your name,
"但这几天里我会找到你的"
but one of these days I'm gonna find you,
"我会把这封信给你为了让你记着你做过的一切"
and I'm gonna give you this letter so you'll remember what you done to me.
"你杀了我的父母Sawyer先生"
You killed my parents, Mr. Sawyer.
现在亲我一个怎样?
Now how about that kiss?
我看你未必会
I didn't think so.
昨天黄昏的时候你在哪?
where were you last night around sunset?
恐怕知道我在哪儿的唯一目击者
Well, I'm afraid the only witness to my whereabouts is
是那只我剥皮用来当晚餐的野猪
the boar that I was skinning for our dinner.
我听说你试图发射求救信号
I heard you were trying to send out a distress call,
那就是说
so it would seem
不管是谁攻击你那家伙一定有不想离开这个岛的理由
whoever attacked you has a reason for not wanting to get off the island.
也许是有个人在当前状况下能拿到一定的好处
Maybe someone who is profiting from our current circumstances.
还有依我看你和Sawyer先生之间有仇
And from what I've seen, you and mr. Sawyer share a certain animosity.
不会是他  他有不在场的证明
No, he has an alibi.
就在我被攻击之前
Just before I was struck,
他还用炮筒发射了一个信号发射的地点在事发地两公里之外
he set off a bottle rocket, a signal we'd worked out 2 kilometers away.
他不可能有时间从...
He couldn't have had the time to go from...
除非他找到一个延迟引燃导火线的方法
unless he found a way to time-delay the fuse on his rocket.
他怎么可能有
How could he possibly have
只要看过电视的人都知道如何即时制作一个延时导火线
anyone who watches television knows how to improvise a slow fuse.
用一根香烟
Use a cigarette.
以后的事  都得以防万一
Just in case there's a next time.
试着吸气...吸气
Just try to breathe. Breathe.
加油  Shannon配合一下
Come on, Shan, work with me.
把呼吸器给我
Give me the inhalers...
现在就给我
Now.
你什么时候可以乖乖闭嘴?
Hell, I wondered when you were gonna stop asking nice.
是时候了  牛仔
Well, it's about time, cowboy.
第一天在野外的时候我就告诉过你
I've been telling you since day one we're in the wild.
看来你一个耳朵进  一个耳朵出
Didn't think you had it in you.
你就只会这些?
That all you got?
我不认为这是一个很好的主意
I'm not sure this is such a good idea.
为什么不?
Why not?
因为朋友间做生意总觉得有点困难
Because business between friends is always a little sticky.
我不了解你但我了解你的妻子
I don't know you well, but I know your wife.
以一种自动代理的方式和她合作
Working with her at the auto dealership.
我不知道这样是否合适
I'm just not sure I'm comfortable.
Louisiana将投资钻井费用的三分之二
Louisiana will invest two-thirdsof the drilling cost.
这算什么  堵枪眼吗?
What is this, a loophole?
听着  David我知道你有点勉为其难
Look, David, you're reluctant.I get it.
你有个牧场你并不需要这个
You got your lumberyard,you don't need this.
我们应该拿下这笔投资
We should do this.
Jess  我甚至不认识这个家伙
Jess, I don't even know this guy.
给他看现金
Show him the cash.
我怎么知道这是真钞?
How do I know this is real?
钱?
The money?
要不要在你那放一晚?
Hell, how about you hold on to it for a night.
核查一下
Check it out.
这样你可以放心一点
I want you to feel secure.
还是不要了
Let's not do this.
我还有个已经出价的投资者
I've got another investor who's committed.
-David  -午饭钱应该够了
-David.  -That should cover lunch.
-还有我们礼拜一见 -David
-And I'll see you Monday.-David
等等
Wait.
暖和的绒毛巾
Warm, fluffy towels.
Banoffie派
Banoffi pie.
这个你已经说过了
You already said that.
乳汁糖还有奶油
Toffee and cream. Mmm.
你想念的只有食物?
Is food the only thing that you miss?
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
难道你就没有渴求得到的东西?
I mean, do you not crave anything?
泡菜炸冰淇淋巧克力
Pickles? Fried ice cream?Chocolate...
花生黄油
Peanut butter.
我是唯一一个喜欢花生黄油的澳大利亚人
I'm the only Australian who loves peanut butter.
我可以给你弄到花生黄油
I can get you peanut butter.
-你当然能了  -真的我能弄到
-Yeah. Sure you can.  -Yes, I can.
我一拿到花生黄油
When I get you peanut butter
你就得离开这个沮丧的沙滩搬到山洞那儿去住
you vacate this shore of depression and move to the caves.
成交?
Deal?
救命  她无法呼吸了!
Help! She's not breathing!
发作得越来越厉害了!
The attacks are getting worse.
Shannon  听我说 看着我看着我
Shannon  Listen to me.
你现在听我说
You need to listen now.
这已经不只是哮喘问题了
This isn't just the asthma.
-这是一种焦虑  -不是
-It's anxiety.  -no.
在你的脑中就是的
It's in your head
你知道药物用完了然后你就很恐慌
Yes.You know that your medicine's run out, and you're panicking.
Shannon...Shannon 看着我
Shannon. Look at me.
我们会共同度过难关的,好吗?
But we can fight this.Together. Okay?
点头就行Shannon
Nod your head, Shannon.
-吸气  -她需要呼吸器  -Boone!
-Breathe in...  -She needs her inhaler.  -Boone!
慢慢地用鼻子吸气
Breathe in through the nose slowly.
不...用鼻子...像这样
No, no, no, no. In through the nose like this.
你能做到  Shannon  你能行
You can do this, Shannon. You can do it.
用鼻子吸气
In through the nose.
你的呼吸顺畅了
You got your breath.
你的血色恢复了我就知道你能行
Your color's coming back. See, I knew you could do this.
-感觉到了吗?  -是的
-You feel it?  -Yeah.
呼吸通畅了好的...再来一次
It's passing. Okay. Again.
用鼻子吸
In through the nose.
很好就这么做
All right. Just keep doing that.
就这么做  你做得很好
Keep breathing like that. That's perfect. Good job.
让她放松
Keep her relaxed.
-不要让她惊慌  -好的
-Do not let her panic.  -Yeah.
老兄  这真让人敬畏
man, that was awesome.
我是说这真是一个
I mean, that was like a...
绝处逢生
jedi moment.
Jack!
如果她拿不到药情况会怎样?
What will happen if she doesn't get her medicine?
看来我们不得不让Sawyer把药交出来
Then we have to make Sawyer give it to us.
是的那就是我要做的
Yeah. That's what I'm gonna do.
不是你做 我上
No, not you. Me.
我在共和卫队服役了5年
I served five years in the republican guard.
我以为你是个通讯军官
I thought you were a communications officer.
训练内容也包括怎样与敌人沟通
Part of my training entailed getting the enemy to communicate.
给我10分钟就行
Just give me 10 minutes with him.
他会把药交出来的
He'll give us the medicine.
你同意了?
Is that a yes?
是的
Yes.
飞机上的食物已经吃完快一个礼拜了老兄
Food from the plane's been gone over a week, dude.
什么没有应急储备了吗?
What, no secret stash for emergencies?
你和Jack在洞里放了一大堆的东西
You and Jack have got a bunch of stuff in that cave.
抱歉老兄 没有花生黄油花生也没  什么都没有
Sorry, man. No peanut butter, no peanuts, no nothing.
但总有什么东西吧?你看看你自己
Yeah, but there's got to be something. I mean, look at you.
看什么?
Look at what?
不不听着
No, no, listen...
胖的人会藏食物?你是不是这么想?
Fat guy hoarding the food? Is that what you think?
不是! 只是我们在这儿已经两礼拜了你知道而你一点儿都...
No! It's just we've been here for two weeks, you know, and you've not really
-我只要一包花生就行  -可我连食物都没有?
-All I need's a bag of peanuts.  -I have no food, all right?
从皮带刻痕来看我已经瘦了一圈了
And for the record, I'm down a notch on my belt.
我是个大家伙
I'm a big guy.
等到你能看出我瘦下来那得花很长时间明白吗?
It's gonna be a while before you're gonna wanna give me a piggy-back ride, okay?
对不起
Sorry.
这真是个很糟糕的体型
That was bad form.
是的  我习惯了
Yeah, I'm used to it.
-所以连一包都没...  -老兄啊!
-So, not even a bag of...  -Dude!
好吧  抱歉
Okay. All right, I'm sorry.
真是该死...
Damn stupid...
Michael
那个生病的女孩
The sick girl...
-有哮喘  -是的...哮喘
-Yeah, asthma.  -Yes, asthma.
我想我能够帮她
I think I can help her.
早上好
Good morning.
你俩干什么?
What are you doing?
Jack!
Sawyer自己找的不是我想惹麻烦
This was Sawyer's choice, not mine.
如果你这样做...
If you do this...
你胆子很大么怎么就趁人打盹的时候打劫?!
Well, ain't you the brave one? Jumping a guy while he's napping.
看来我真有麻烦了 是吗?
I'm in trouble now, ain't I?
Sawyer
我们给你个改过自新的机会
we gave you a chance to do the right thing.
我想要的只是哮喘药你只需告诉我呼吸器在哪
Now all I want is the asthma medicine. Just tell me where the inhalers are,
我们就停手
and we'll stop.
停什么? chico(一种灌木这里指Jack)?
Stop what, chico?
你本不必承受这种痛苦的
It doesn't have to be this way.
是的  确实不必
Yeah, it does.
伊拉克没有竹子
We do not have bamboo in Iraq.
但有相似的东西...芦苇
Although we do have something similar...reeds.
效果是一样的
But their effect is the same...
当竹尖插入指甲里面
when the chutes are inserted underneath the fingernails.
你知道我在想什么吗 Ali(穆罕默德的女婿)
You know what I think, Ali?
我认为你这辈子还没有折磨过人
I think you've never actually tortured anybody in your life.
看来我俩都很不辛
Unfortunately for us both
你错了
you're wrong.
就这样?
That's it?
你就这点能耐?
That's all you got?
刺片?
Splinters?
毫无疑问我们在哥斯湾痛扁你们
No wonder we kicked your ass in the gulf...aah!
Sayid
Sayid!
不要
No.
不要停
Don't stop now.
我想我的呼吸很顺畅了
I think my sinuses are clearing.
你这人到底怎么回事?
What the hell is wrong with you?
也许挖出你的眼睛
Perhaps losing an eye
能让你打开金口
will loosen your tongue.
好吧!
Okay!
好
Okay
在哪?
Where is it?
我只告诉
Only person I'll tell...
她
is her.
Kate?
这是交易
That's the deal.
告诉我  Sawyer你想死吗?
Tell me, Sawyer, do you want to die?
因为当一个人走进我的房子
Cause when a man walks into my place
告诉我他把16万血汗钱交给一个普通市民保管
and tells me he left 160,000 of my hard-won dollars in the care of a civilian...
我得问问自己听到的是不是一个请求解脱的
I got to ask myself if what I'm hearing isn't
绝望的呼喊
a desperate cry for the sweet release of death.
今天交易达成了
Deal closed today.
看女人就是简单
See, women are easy.
给些温柔给她们看看新鲜的床上功夫
A few cosmos, a couple of stunts they hadn't seen between the sheets
她们会认为整个骗局是她们的点子
and they think the scam's their idea.
还有丈夫们...他们需要触到钱嗅一嗅
Now, the husbands...they need to touch the money, smell it.
认为如果他们有实力吞下别人的钱
Believe that if they had the brass to put that suitcase
他们就会乖乖的听你话
in the trunk of their family sedan and speed away
然后找机会伪装成个老实的坏蛋
they just might have a chance at being an honest-to-gosh outlaw.
好吧  Tex 如果可以这么轻易的骗到钱
Okay, Tex, if you got your grift so pat,
那你还要我的钱干什么?
what'd you need my money for?
你在上对夫妻中骗到的钱哪去了?
Where's your seed from the last couple you wrote?
我该怎么说呢?
Well, what can I say?
我喜欢赚的和花的一样多
I like earning it as much as I like spending it.
不过无论如何
Be that as it may
我还是知道一两个折磨人的方法
I know a thing or two about making people suffer.
现在你拿了我的钱在明天中午之前外加50%的利息一同还我
Now, you have my money, plus 50% by noon tomorrow,
否则我会告诉你该如何折磨人
or I'll tell you all about it.
我来了  东西在哪儿?
So I'm here. Where is it?
很乐意告诉你
Happy to tell you
只要你亲我
as soon as I get that kiss.
什么?  你是认真的?
What? Are you serious?
宝贝儿  这儿是个神秘的丛林我被绑在了树上
Baby, I am tied to a tree in the jungle of mystery.
刚刚还被一个他妈的骨科医生和一个真正的伊拉克人折磨过
I just got tortured by a damn spinal surgeon and a genuine iraqi.
我当然是认真的
Of course I'm serious.
你不会看到刚才的大场面  雀斑女
You're just not seeing the big picture here, freckles.
你真想让那女孩窒息而死?!
Are you really gonna let that girl suffocate
就因为你无法忍受给我一个"吻"?
cause you can't bring yourself to give me one little kiss?
妈的  那可是最低要求了
Hell, it's only first base.
你还算幸运我并不贪心
Lucky for you, I ain't greedy.
好
Okay.
我没有
I don't have it.
什么?
What?
药
The medicine.
我没那个药  从来就没有过
I don't have it. I never did.
那本书
The book...
他们说你在他们的行李中找到的
they said you found it in their luggage.
书  连同其他的一切
Book washed up on shore.
都被冲到了岸边
It went in the drink with the rest of...
他并没有药
He doesn't have it.
-什么?  -他在说谎  难道看不出来?
-What?  -He's lying. Can't you see that?
他从一开始就在撒谎
He's been lying from the beginning.
他不想让我们离开这个岛
He doesn't want us to get off this island.
-那就是他袭击我的原因  -等等  伙计
-That's why he attacked me.  -Hold on a minute, man.
-他损坏了接收机  -你并不知道
-He destroyed the transceiver.  -You don't know that.
Sayid!
他切中动脉了
He hit an artery.
不要动!  该死...
Keep still, damn it.
Sayid 山洞里有我要的东西就在我的皮背包里  快去!
Sayid, I need my stuff from the caves. My leather backpack. Go!
能止住血吗?
Can you make it stop?
这是谁的血?
Whose blood is that?
谁的血?
Sawyer
你去追Sawyer却不告诉我一声?
You went after Sawyer, and you didn't even tell me?
-她是我妹妹  -Boone
-She's my sister.  -Boone.
不要留我一个人在这儿好吗?
Don't leave me alone, okay?
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
好吗?
Okay?
好
Okay.
是这些吗?我想树是找对了,但...
Are these the right ones? I think I found the right tree, but...
哦是的太好了
Oh, yes. Good.
不要...老兄
Don't, man.
我告诉你
I'm telling you...
不要那样
Don't.
别管我
Let go.
我知道你根本不想关心我
I know you want to.
闭嘴  不要动
Shut up, and stop moving.
你一直在等这个机会是不是?
You've been waiting for this, haven't you?
现在你又成英雄了
Now you get to be a hero again,
因为你就是这么做的你总会把事情伪装得很完美
cause that's what you do. You fix everything up all nice.
是时候松开了  雀斑女我们已经亲热过了
Time to let go, freckles. We already made out.
我还有什么好奢求的?
What else I got to live for?
Jack你得记住
Hey, Jack, there's something you should know.
如果我们现在处境交换的话
If the tables were turned...
我会看着你死
I'd watch you die.
很好
All righty.
看来我们在石油生意上达成一致了
Looks like we're in the oil business.
就这样行了?  -哦行了
We're cool?  -Oh, we're cool.
我们把钱取回来  -明天之后的一个礼拜增值三倍
We get the money back...  -A week from tomorrow. Tripled.
你不会逃之夭夭吧  会吗?
You're not gonna skip town, are you?
David看老天的份上!
David, for god's sake!
他的钱都在我们这儿要逃的也该是我们
He left all his money with us. We could have skipped town.
你有个聪明的女人 David  不要让她给跑了
Smart woman you got there, David. Don't let her go.
宝贝儿
Hi, baby.
怎么起来了?  感觉好点了吗?
What are you doing up? Are you feeling better?
念故事给我听好吗?
Will you read to me?
马上就来  宝贝 我们现在有客人
In a minute, sweetheart. We have company right now.
你没事吧?
You okay?
交易取消
Deal's off.
你说什么? -交易取消  就此结束
Excuse me?-Deal's off. Forget it.
你这是干什么?  -等等这算什么玩笑?
What are you doing?  -Hold on. What is this, a joke?
取消了就是取消了 我得走了
I'm calling it off, walking away.
不许走
You're not walking out of here.
你知道我为了这个付出多少要我一天之内取到这么多钱?
You know what I had to do for this, all this money in one day?
把手拿开小子-Sawyer!-这到底怎么回事?
Take your hand off me, boy.-Sawyer!-What's going on here?
结果不应该是这样的
This is isn't how it wassupposed to work.
你说过我们...  -他说什么了 Jessica?!
You said that we were... -What did he say, Jessica?!
活着算你走运
You're lucky to be alive.
回洞里检查Shannon去了
Went to the caves to check on Shannon.
我又读了一遍
I read it again.
又一遍
And then again,
因为我想搞明白你为什么打Boone
because I've been trying to figure out why you beat up Boone
而不直接告诉他 你没有他妹妹的药物
instead of just telling him you didn't have his sister's medication.
但你又为什么要假装有呢!
Why you pretended to have it anyway.
我唯一想得到的解释是 你想要大家都恨你
The thing that I keep coming back around to is that you want to be hated.
然后我看了看信封
Then I looked at the envelope.
"美国两百周年纪念诺克斯维尔田纳西州"
"America's bicentennial. Knoxville, Tennessee."
那时你还是个孩子8岁或许9岁
You were just a kid. 8, maybe 9 years old.
这封信不是写给你的是你自己写的
This letter wasn't written to you. You wrote this letter.
你名字不叫Sawyer是吧?
Your name's not Sawyer, is it?
那是他的名字
It was his name.
他是个自信的男人
He was a confidence man.
和我妈妈搞关系又拿到了钱
Romanced my mama to get to the money.
然后擦擦屁股走人  留下一堆屎
Wiped them out clean, left a mess behind.
所以我写了那封信
So I wrote that letter.
我写了信  以为我会找到他的
I wrote it knowing one day I'd find him.
这还不算是最悲哀的部分
But that ain't the sad part.
我19岁的时候
When I was 19,
需要6000美金来还给那些和我有关系的家伙
I needed 6 grand to pay these guys off I was in trouble with.
所以我找了个漂亮的女人 她老公是个聋子很有钱
So I found a pretty lady with a dumb husband who had some money.
我成功的让他把钱给了我
And I got him to give it to me.
那是怎样的一种悲哀?
我变成了我苦苦追寻的那个人
I became the man I was hunting.
我变成了Sawyer
I became Sawyer.
不用同情我
Don't you feel sorry for me.
离开这儿
Get the hell out.
滚开
Get out!
我不知道  感觉这就像个奇迹
I don't know. It's like some miracle.
她就弄了些混合物
She just showed upwith that mixture.
擦在Shannon的胸部10分钟后她居然能呼吸了
She rubbed it on Shannon's chest, and 10 minutes later she was breathing.
桉树
Eucalyptus.
聪明  Jack
Smart, Jack.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
-你在干什么?  -打点你的东西
-What are you doing?  -Packing your stuff.
你要搬到洞里去了
You're moving to the caves.
你不会吧?
You didn't?
花生黄油?
Peanut butter?
不可能吧!  -你预定的呀
No way!  -Just like you ordered.
不过有件事
Oh. There is one thing.
那东西特别的油滑
It's extra smooth.
没关系
That's okay.
是空的
It's empty.
不
No.
不不  是满的
No, it's not. It's full.
都满到瓶口了
Full to the brim with...
粘到你嘴的上颚去了
stick-to-the-roof-of-your-mouth,
老天  它让我想喝杯牛奶
oh, God, it makes you want a glass of milk,
特别的油滑
extra smooth...
这是我尝过的最美味的花生黄油
it's the best bloody peanut butter I've ever tasted.
要来点吗?
You want some?
Sayid
-我不能再呆下去了  -什么?
-I can't stay here.  -What?
我要离开我也不知道要多久
I'm leaving. I don't know for how long.
Sayid你不能这样
Sayid, you can't.
我们还不知道那是什么东西
We still don't know what's out there.
比起丛林怪物有些东西更让我感到可怕
I have worse things to fear than what's in the jungle.
我今天做的事...
What I did today...
我今天差点就做的事
what I almost did...
我发誓我再不会这么做了
I swore to do never again.
如果我不能遵守诺言
If I can't keep that promise
我没权力呆在这儿
I have no right to be here.
我没地方可去
There's no where to go.
但必须得有人走遍这个海岸画好这座岛屿的地图
Someone has to walk the shore and map the island,
去看看还有什么东西在这儿
see what else there is.
我找不到一个更适合做这件事的人 我只相信我自己
I can't think of a better person to do it than the only one I trust.
希望还能再次和你相遇
I hope we meet again.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====
YYeTs美剧翻译组制作
更多精彩欢迎登录YYeTs美剧天堂论坛
www.YYETS.net